Thai Truong 14 Isabella Apartment, SE13 7DU Tel: 07513021305

Email: sontruong@hotmail.co.uk

Enthusiastic self-taught front-end developer with a focus on building robust and accessible interfaces. I am knowledgeable in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, with a passion to build accessible web applications and learning new technologies. A sharp eye for detail with experience in QA testing and an understanding of agile environments and version control.

Employment History

April 2019 - Present

Digital Officer Lambeth Council

- Converted wireframes into web components using HTML and CSS.
- Responsible for QA testing to support continuous deployment of environment.
- Collaborated with developers to ensure accessibility, design and development were met.
- Restyling templates to the CMS (Drupal) using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Carried out regular site maintenance including link-checking, accessibility checks, site reliability, archiving and audience usage analysis.
- Influenced a range of staff in the relevant teams to take ownership of their digital content by coaching, negotiating with and training key staff.
- Integrating forms to an electronic document management system.
- Engaging with stakeholders to understand business needs and managing issues through a help desk system.

July 2016 - December 2018

Digital Marketing Executive Neogrid

- Designing and implementing email marketing campaigns and landing pages.
- Creating sales deck/collaterals and redesigning the company's website.
- Executing event-marketing strategy for tradeshows and conferences, organising event logistics, promotions and working within tradeshow booths.
- Creating reports using analytics tools such Google AdWords and Lead Forensics.

Skills

Language: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, SCSS/SASS, React, NPM

Framework: Tailwind, Bootstrap

CMS: Drupal

Version management: Git, Github Project management: JIRA IDE: Visual studio code Other: Figma, Miro, WCAG 2.1

Achievements

- Completed a 3-month web development course at General Assembly.
- Involved in redesigning, testing and launching of a new website for Lambeth Council

Education & Qualification

Coventry University (2012-2015)

BA Advertising & Marketing – 2:1

Luton Sixth Form College (2010-2012)

References

Provided on request